Guide to the Arleen Schloss Papers MSS.437
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Performances and Exhibitions, 1960-2013; 82.4 Linear Feet in 44 cassette boxes, 33 record cartons, 12 manuscript boxes, 5 LP boxes, 5 flat files, and 4 flat boxes; 665 audiocassettes; 202 Hi8; 170 VHS; 137 MiniDV; 78 U-matic; 58 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 29 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 4 Betamax
  - Subseries I.C: Events by Date, 1967-2013
    - Mania D Blässe, Werner Nurprivat, December 14, 1979; FA_MSS_437_ER_4
    - "4 in 1" Composition, 1979; cuid44161
      - Audio, cuid44162 (Box 155, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2433)
      - Audio, cuid44163 (Box 155, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2434)
      - Audio with "AAA" section (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0327)
      - New Wilderness Foundation Log (Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 9)
    - Bottles, circa 1979 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0180)
    - Buzzing of Lips, Greece, 1979; cuid44182
      - Audio recording, cuid44165 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2428)
      - New Wilderness Foundation Log (Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 11)
    - Castle Lengenfeld, Austria, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Compilation Tape -- Ray's water music, Hank Bill performance, Interview with Swiss radio, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0623)
      Full label reads: "Humanic tape 79, 2 min 14 sec, Arleen Schloss, some of Ray's Watermusic and Hank Bill performance, last part, and interview, Swiss Radio"
    - "Composition 5 in 1", 1979 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0390)
      Produced by Arleen Schloss and Charlie Morrow, recorded at New Wilderness Studios under Artists Access program
    - Performance in Basel, Switzerland, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Projekt Audio Scene, Vienna, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Performances at LERM, Düsseldorf, 1979-1980
      - Video, 1979 (Box 145, Half inch video reel 437_1960)
      - "Adventure A" and Shot Dot Shot, September, 1979 (Box 124, U-matic 437_1562)
        Duration: 20 minutes
        Video by Alex Schneider
      - "Adventure A", Evening in Köln, September 7-8, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0683)
      - Blässe, Vocals and Rhythm, April 5, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0636)
    - Liquid Idiot and Idiot Orchestra, circa 1979-1980; FA_MSS_437_ER_6
    - Two tape mix, circa 1979-1980; cuid44166 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0853)
    - Creative Artists Public Service Program Fellowship, 1979 - 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Robert L. Sanders Demos, 1979-1983
      - "I Believe in UFOs," The Mars Song, 1979 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0155)
      - "Stop Stealing My Light", 1982 (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0131)
      - Audio, 1982 (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0229)
      - "You're Crazy, I Love You!", 1982 (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0289)
      - "Dance!", "Stop Stealing My Light," "You're Crazy, I Love You!", circa 1982-1983 (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0110)
      - "Time to Change," "You're Crazy, I Love You!," "Loretta", 1983 (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0116)
      - "Lone Star of Amarillo," "Gringo," "Loretta", 1983 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0378)
    - "A Team Performances", 1979-1985
      - A's at SNAFU, Burta Alphabet, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0240)
      - Jorgeo Gallo, Flo No Rehearsal, 1980 (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0245)
      - Arleen and Flo No, July 9, 1980 (Box 112, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2273)
        Label also reads: "Echocity Arleen plays all: bass, rhythm ace, voice, (illegible)"
      - Flo No at Plugg, July 18, 1980 (Box 69, Audiocassette 437_0197)
      - Flo No Rehearsal at Plugg, July 24, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0848)
      - Flo No at Plugg, July 25, 1980 (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0084)
      - Sandra McKee, Phoebe Legere, Meta Monad, September 17, 1980 (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0230)
      - Virgil Moorefield at CBGB, December, 1981 - January, 1982 (Box 69, Audiocassette 437_0214)
      - "Valentine's Day Sound," "Phenomenal Women" by Howie Solo, 1983 (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0225)
      - Audio, March 1, 1985 (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0271)
    - Ear Magazine Benefits, 1979-1986
      - #2, May 25, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0613)
      - 425 Broome Street, Paco's piece, Alphabet, May 25, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0688)
      - Ephemera, 1983 - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Arleen Schloss MC's, 4D, undated (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0830)
    - Exhibit and Event Invitations, 1979 - 2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - A's News -- Poster, circa 1980s (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Compilation Tape -- Alphabet, It's a Live Laser, Opera, "A-Z", A's Des Refuses", circa 1980s (Box 128, Vhs 437_1598)
    - Compilation Tape -- How She Sees It, Collage of Performances, circa 1980s (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0157)
    - Flo No Performance, circa 1980s (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0272)
    - Flo No, Phoebe Legere, Monad, circa 1980s (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0235)
    - HG, Andrea Gibson, Pauline, circa 1980s (Box 141, Vhs 437_1915)
    - Jarrow sticks, I Ching, Cage, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 140, Vhs 437_1869)
    - Nina I Ching, John Cage, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 123, Vhs 437_1162)
    - "Chemicals Made From Dirt", January, 1980 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0364)
    - Country music, rhythm machine, January, 1980 - June, 1981 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0841)
    - "Before Berlin" Studio Sessions, January 2, 1980; cuid44169
      - "Two cuts", cuid44170 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0838)
      - Audio recording, cuid44171 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2429)
      - New Wilderness Foundation Log (Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 8)
    - Vocals and rhythm box, January 3, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0834)
    - It's an A Performances, Café Einstein, Berlin, January, 1980
      - Audio, January 3, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0640)
      - Ephemera, January 13 - 14, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Audio, January 14, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0856)
    - Benefit for R.L. Seltman -- Arcadians, Toxic Shock, Elephant Dance, Liquid Liquid, January 17, 1980; cuid44119 (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0279)
    - Rehearsal, Ear Inn, February 8, 1980 - February 3, 1986 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0831)
      Includes Arleen Schloss, Winn, John, Jaine, Tod
    - David Arnet, February 8, 1980 (Box 112, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2274)
    - Echo Party at SNAFU -- Arleen Schloss and Thomas, Phoebe Legere, Monad, March 13, 1980 (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0232)
    - Arleen Schloss Vocals, Conversation with Capy from Moon, March 13-26, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0850)
    - Sound and other experiments at Hedda's, December 25, 1977 - January 7, 1978 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0922)
    - Live Performance, Mo/on, Berlin, March 25-26, 1980
      - Audio, March 25-26, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0646)
      - Audio, March 26, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0647)
      - Ephemera, March 26, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 10, Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Modern Art Gallery Solo, Vienna, Austria, March 28, 1980 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0635)
    - Rhythm Box Performance, Berlin, March 28, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0832)
      Featuring Arleen Schloss; Eva Gossling - sax; Alexander - synthesizer; Michel Richard - synthesizer
    - Performance with Blässe, Modern Art Gallery, Vienna, March 28, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0645)
    - "Stimme / Rhythmusmaschine / Super8 Film / Dias," Modern-Art Galerie, Vienna, March 28, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Performances by Beth Anderson, Paul Zaloom, Jacki Apple, A Band!, April 1, 1980
      - Audio (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0281)
      - Audio (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0282)
    - "S.T.I.P." Performance, Franklin Furnace, April 17, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - The 12th International Sound Poetry Festival, Washington Square Church, April 19, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Performance by Arleen Schloss, Washington Square Church, April 19, 1980 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0634)
    - "Visual Dias" Performances, S.N.A.F.U., May, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - A hums, May 1-8, 1980 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0632)
    - Artist Talk -- "The Dynamics of Collaboration" Panel, May 2, 1980
      This panel features Claire Ferguson, Tod Jorgenson, Peter Frank, and Ken Friedman.
      - Audio (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0286)
      - Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - "Performance dite artistique?" Lecture and Music by Arleen Schloss, D'une Certain Gaiete, May 15, 1980
      - Audio (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0633)
      - Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 15, Box 65, Folder 9)
    - "La Nuit Parcourt Le Ciel Poesie a la Limite du Son," Argenteau Coal Mine, May 16, 1980
      - Audio (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0649)
      - Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 16, Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    - Liege -- Afternoon and Evening, May 17, 1980 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0373)
    - Instrumental, Heroes Paris, May 22, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0851)
    - Performances in Boston, June 7, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0644)
      Full label reads: "J + LL Krosen performance in Boston, Arleen Schloss performance work in Boston with kids"
    - The National Center of Afro-American Artists Intermedia Performance, Franklin Furnace, June 7, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - A's Little Berlin Cabaret at the Space, June 14, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Vocals, guitar, rhythmace, June 21, 1980 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0890)
    - Shell Shock Rock, Belfast Ireland, Manhattan Project, August 3, 1980 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0040)
    - David Bower on TV, Arleen singing, September, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0849)
      Label on case reads: "Bowie: Tin Machine, Reed: New York"
    - Mediations in Simplicity, New York City, October 7, 1980 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0876)
    - Staten Island Ferry Diamond Jubilee, October 25, 1980
      - Project Meeting, A's Theme Song (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0280)
      - Planning documentation, ephemera, and photographs (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_437_ER_7
    - Rhythm, keyboard, voice, telephone, December 15, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0637)
    - "100% Synthetiks" Performance, Düsseldorf, circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2, Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Franklin Furnace -- Selection Committee Correspondence, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Music from S/O, Berlin, 1980 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0837)
    - Singing, Alphabet, 1980 (Box 80, Audiocassette 437_0651)
    - Watch Out Never Mind Anyway..., 1980 (Box 114, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0543)
    - Tara Cyndi Talk, Collage from Germany, 1980-1981 (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0569)
    - Artists Talk on Art Panels, 1980 - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Marbleyes, 1980-1996
      - Marble Prototypes, 1980 (Box 130, Vhs 437_1624)
      - Video, 1988 (Box 131, U-matic 437_1679)
      - Video, 1990 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2157)
      - Video, circa 1990 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1742)
      - Video with original sound, circa 1990 (Box 131, Vhs 437_1697)
      - The Kitchen, March, 1990 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2093)
      - The Kitchen, March, 1990 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2112)
      - China PS1, June 1, 1990 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2056)
      - Marble Events, Bremen, Germany, circa early 1990s (Box 122, Vhs 437_1137)
      - Video, 1996 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1721)
      - Edit, Master, undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1818)
    - "Der Andere Aspekt," Dany Keller Galerie, February 6, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Performances 81, Städtische Galerie, February 10 - 20, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Lenbachhaus Performance, Munich, February 19, 1981
      - Audio (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0604)
      - Audio (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0601)
      - Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Krupps Stahlwerksinfonie, Komödii Trakik, March 20-28, 1981 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0153)
    - Confession Under Luna, Maison A's, March 25, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "The New York from the Performance," The First National Congress on Women in Music, March 26 - 29, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Arleen Schloss, Jacki Apple, Information, Robert Sanders, April 2, 1981 (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0285)
    - P.I.M. Magazine and A's News Benefit, April 11, 1981 (Box 69, Audiocassette 437_0220)
      Featuring Susan and Steve Levine, Steve Larson and Eric Schmidt, Bill Ross, Peter Cummings, Sandra McKee, A Christian From Outer Space, Claire Ferguson, Bob Holman and Vito Ricci, Angela Hans, Barbara Allen, Carol Clements, Winora Schwartz, Eliot Sharpe, Buster Cleveland and friends, Arleen Schloss, Charly Dennis, and Diane Torr.
    - "Scalp-Tone Direct-Line Hard-Edge Haircuts", April 21, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Compilation Tape -- Monster Mash, A-Z Performance, Greenspace performance, Robert Sanders, May 8, 1981 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0599)
    - Guitar text samples, June, 1981 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0724)
      Label also reads: "Shore and conk shells, Patti, Angela, Arleen's vocals of text and guitar and snowing, Ginny and Casio"
    - "Inky Dinky Spider," Arleen and Claire, June 11, 1981 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0320)
    - Cassio memory repetition, Robert Parker reading How She Sees It, June 20, 1981 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0712)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Cassio memory repetition, country music / Side B: Reciting from Henig tape, disco news, at end Robert Parker reading How She Sees It"
    - Compilation Tape -- Collage of sound performances, How She Sees It by Her, July 7, 1981 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0783)
    - Tape at Ernie's, July 7, 1981 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0606)
    - Black Lake, August, 1981 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0714)
    - Practice for Regina International -- Arleen, Anna, Barb, Randy A's story, October 9-31, 1981 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0374)
    - Sheila Dhar, November 29, 1981 (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0121)
    - Big guitar and ticks -- A, Angela's tape, 1981 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0836)
    - Bones -- Victor Milt, 1981 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0940)
    - Performance Compilation -- "Mouth Eye," MoMA, How She Sees It By Her, 1981; FA_MSS_437_ER_10
    - Sandy Cies Performance, Frank Marino Gallery, 1981 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0372)
    - How She Sees It, 1981-1983
      - Collage, different voices, 1981 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0711)
      - New Wilderness Audiographics, 1981 (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0485)
      - Compilation Tape -- How She Sees It, Belize, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0798)
      - Audio, circa 1981 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0602)
      - Background music, Courtney, Laugh at telephone, circa 1981 (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0079)
      - Piano composition, circa 1981 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0394)
      - Last day, René's piece, Arleen's performance, music circle, July 23-24, 1981 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0718)
      - Arleen and Michael, Arleen and Cathy, October, 1981 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0729)
      - Collage, November, 1981 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0702)
      - Chris, Guitar, Cathy, 1982 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0710)
      - Video Master, January - February, 1982 (Box 151, U-matic 437_0020)
      - Performance, Pyramid Club, May, 1982 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0723)
      - Tin Pan Alley Performance, Kwok, May, 1982 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0777)
        Label also reads: "How She Sees It, German, English, Spanish"
      - "I Don't Want to Know You," "Helmut", May 17, 1982 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0384)
      - Electronic Records, 1983; FA_MSS_437_ER_13
      - New Wilderness Audiographics Ephemera, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Original, piano, 1983 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0726)
      - Fan-voice sound experiments, April 2, 1983 (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0052)
    - Compilation Tape -- Performance excerpts, 1981-1984 (Box 115, U-matic 437_1074)
    - How She Sees It By Her, 1981-2009
      This multimedia performance is described by Schloss as "an epic poem translated into noise performance."
      - Notebook, circa 1981 (Box 61)
      - Performance Ephemera, June 6, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9, 10, 11, 12)
      - Posters, 1981 - 1982 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Video, 1981-1983 (Box 123, U-matic 437_1170)
        Transfer from Super 8mm film
      - Arleen and Cathy, Montreal Performance, February 20, 1982 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0738)
      - Musak Noise Sound Festival Ephemera, February 20, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Audio, July 13, 1982 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0539)
      - Banner, Club Armageddon, July 15, 1982 (Box 65)
      - A work in progress, 1982 (Box 141, U-matic 437_1886)
      - Audio, circa 1982 (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0576)
      - Start, piano and split screen, 1982 (Box 123, U-matic 437_1171)
      - Arleen, Bruce, and Trish, Interludes, December 29, 1984 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0767)
      - Voice, drums, radio, rhythm, 1987 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0892)
        Label also reads: "Made on 3rd St., Arleen - later parts, blurry voice, drums and radio"
      - Video, October 24, 2009 (Box 95, Minidv 437_1454)
    - "I Love You" -- People, chorus, rehearsal, January 3, 1982 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0600)
    - Cut Into Her -- Rehearsal with Anna Barbs, March, 1982 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0461)
    - "Poetry is Music" Radio Series, March, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 15, Box 10, Folder 41, Box 65, Folder 21)
    - "A's on the Air," WBAI, May 12, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - New Wilderness Summer Solstice Celebration, June 21, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - "Projects" Exhibit, Hansen Fine Arts, Inc., July, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Performance A-Z, Storefront for Art and Architecture, September 18 - October 13, 1982
      - Rehearsal audio, September, 1982 (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0124)
      - Press clippings, September 18 - October 13, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 20, Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Electronic Records, 1982; FA_MSS_437_ER_11
      - Video, 1982 (Box 153, U-matic 437_0046)
      - Video, 1982 (Box 115, U-matic 437_1076)
      - Video, 1982 (Box 123, U-matic 437_1219)
      - Video master, 1982 (Box 139, U-matic 437_1891)
      - Video, 1983 (Box 142, U-matic 437_1897)
        Edited by Gretta W. Miller, Arleen Schloss, Richard Skidmore
      - Monster Mash, undated (Box 124, U-matic 437_1504)
      - Video, undated (Box 115, U-matic 437_1094)
      - Video, undated (Box 97, Minidv 437_1542)
    - Dan Goode Wind Symphony Och Orch, Arleen Schloss Pincrossing, October 3, 1982; cuid44174 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0113)
    - "My Name is Nemesis", December, 1982 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0365)
      "From Vernita to Arleen"
    - "N Nite," A's, December 11, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21, Box 61, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 6)
    - A Plastic Performance Collaboration with Kwok Mang Ho -- Proposal, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Artists in the Marketspace -- Tape #2, 1982 (Box 141, U-matic 437_1899)
      Label also reads: "Arleen Schloss introducing Sandra McKee, Michael Keene; X-35 sculpture show; Super8 at end, How She Sees It"
    - CAC, Drum music, Sunshine, All Nite Long, 1982 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0893)
    - Compilation Tape -- Storage material, X-35 with How She Sees It, 1982 (Box 139, U-matic 437_1893)
      Label also reads: "Robert Parker in the Artist's market V.A.P. - slides in front of face with tape and intro - film off wall 0 across st. in studio with Anna (illegible) - boxes on street, chop sticks with sound ... mother 2 father (X-35 Opera How She Sees It tape blank image w/ sound)"
    - Dreamflesh -- "Parts Unknown", 1982 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0326)
    - Germany Performances -- Nina Hagen and others, 1982 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0323)
    - "Live to Air: Artists' Sound Works," Audio Arts Magazine, 1982
      - Magazine (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Part one (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0099)
      - Part two (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0872)
      - Part three (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0057)
    - WBAI, circa 1982-1984; cuid44172
      - How She Sees It By Her, Isaac Jackson, January, 1982 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0381)
      - How She Sees It By Her, Isaac Jackson, January, 1982 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0371)
      - Arleen Schloss, Jack Smead, Bruce Ditmiss, Trish Burgess, 1984; cuid44173 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2424)
      - Audio, June - July, 1984 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0322)
      - Audio, July 9, 1984 (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0592)
      - Arleen Schloss and Friends, December 11, 1984 (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0596)
      - Arleen Schloss and Friends, December 12, 1984 (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0595)
      - Arleen Schloss, Young Marble Giants, Clash, Messages, undated (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0725)
      - Audio, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0109)
      - Audio, undated (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0377)
      - John Kalish and Marilyn Rossner, undated (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0773)
    - Danceteria, 1983-1985
      - Disarmament Circus, May 9, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Video, 1983 (Box 95, Minidv 437_1450)
      - The Barebones Orchestra, Money on My Mins, PS 182, 1000 Balloons, April 14, 1985 (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0132)
      - Clinton's Danceteria, C.A.C., undated (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0739)
    - RESTRICTED: Compilation Tape -- Letterland, Children's Excerpts from 82-83, 1982-1986 (Box 88, Audiocassette 437_0948)
    - Storefront for Art and Architecture Event Ephemera, 1982 - 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1, Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Glen Branca -- Rehearsal, January, 1983 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0717)
      Full label reads: "Glen Branca rehearsal at Wayne Music Studios"
    - Hank Williams, Dave Hickey, Phone messages, January - February, 1983 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0728)
    - Section of clapping, strikeforce, January 23, 1983 (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0126)
    - "Is Performance Art?" Panel, Artists Talk on Art, Soho 20 Gallery, February 18, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Edited Alphabet Project, March 29, 1983 (Box 112, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2275)
    - Bowie -- "Let's Dance," "Space," "Sunshine", April, 1983 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0159)
    - A first time, second time -- 50, CKM, April 16, 1983 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0737)
    - G8 A #40, December 12, 1983 - May 9, 1984 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0735)
    - Rhythmusmaschine, Brussels, May 22-26, 1983 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0741)
    - London Hotel and Pub Performances, Movements #1, May 28-29, 1983 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0329)
      Label also reads: "Side B includes funny taxi sounds taped on train"
    - "New Wilderness on Transfigured Night: 5 Live Concerts on WKCR-FM", June, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Plexus, Richard, June 24, 1983 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0740)
    - The Street Beasties, July 4, 1983 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0136)
    - Musical performances, July 16, 1983 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0742)
      Full label reads: "Side A: July - Cata and Daniela, A at Nose - P on drums, J. (illegible) grime / Side B: A - guitar, Richard M. - trumpet, Dawn drums - A voice"
    - Going to Connie's, August 22-23, 1983 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0692)
    - New York Road Runners -- No Se No Performance, October 12, 1983
      - Art Show Performance -- Original (Box 141, U-matic 437_1888)
      - No Se No Presents Ray Kelly (Box 128, U-matic 437_1611)
      - Audio (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0482)
    - "Moonage Daydream" Exhibition, the Underground, November 16, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Cynthia after midnight, December 30, 1983 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0786)
    - Aktuell(e), Munich, 1983 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0141)
    - Artists Talk on Art, 1983 (Box 120, Vhs 437_1199)
    - Babby and Plastics, 1983 (Box 72, Minidv 437_0299)
    - Branca Symphony No. 3, Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5, Box 65, Folder 13)
    - New Wilderness Summer Solstice Celebration, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Tellus #17: Video Arts Music, 1983; cuid44175